<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">Something</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    //attractions strings
    <string name="attraction_0">Sabarmati Ashram</string>
    <string name="attraction_description_0">"Sabarmati Ashram (also known as Gandhi Ashram, Harijan Ashram, or Satyagraha Ashram) is located in the Sabarmati suburb of Ahmedabad, Gujarat, adjoining the Ashram Road, on the banks of the River Sabarmati, four miles from the town hall. This was one of the residences of Mohandas Karamchand Gandhi, generally called Mahatma Gandhi, who lived there for about twelve years along with his wife, Kasturba Gandhi. It was from his base here that Gandhi led the Dandi march also known as the Salt Satyagraha on 12 March 1930. In recognition of the significant influence that this march had on the Indian independence movement the Indian government has established the ashram as a national monument."</string>
    <string name="attraction_address_0">Gandhi Smarak Sangrahalaya, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380027</string>

    <string name="attraction_1">Vastrapur </string>
    <string name="attraction_description_1">"Vastrapur Lake is situated in western part of Ahmedabad. It is officially named after Narsinh Mehta. The lake was beautified by the AMC after 2002 and has since become a popular spot in the city.
"
                "Every weekend, a large number of people visit this lake. It currently boasts an open-air theater and children's park. There is a pathway all around the lake which serves many walkers and joggers in the early mornings and in the evenings.\n"
                "The lush green lawns surrounding this lake also serve as a central hub of Ahmedabad, wherein various cultural events take place regularly."</string>
    <string name="attraction_address_1">Vastrapur Lake, Vastrapur, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380052</string>

    <string name="attraction_2">Manek Chok</string>
    <string name="attraction_description_2">"This bustling open square near the center of the city functions as a vegetable market in the morning and a jewellery market in the afternoon, the second biggest in India, at an apparently 3 million rupees of annual turnover. It is most famous, however, for its food stalls that start to emerge around 9:30 in the evening and continue till late night, with various local street snacks. Manek chowk is best known for its Kulfi."</string>
    <string name="attraction_address_2">Manek Chowk, Khadia, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380001</string>

    <string name="attraction_3">Rani no Hajiro</string>
    <string name="attraction_description_3">"The courtyard contains eight marble tombs of queens of Ahmed Shah I and other Gujarat Sultanate rulers. They are elaborately carved and inlaid with work of mother-of-pearl and metal.
"
                "The principal tomb belongs to Mughalai Bibi, the wife of Muhammad Shah II and mother of Mahmud Begada. It is richly carved in white marble, and girt with a Persian inscription in minute relief. An adjacent tomb in black marble, once inlaid with mother-of-pearl, belongs to Mirki or Murki Bibi, the wife of Shah e Alam, the sister of queen and the daughter of Jam of Sindh. These tombs are covered with rich brocade works, the textile style developed during reign of Ahmed Shah I. The intricate stone tracery and carving is an amalgamation of Hindu, Jain, and Islamic architectural styles. Some Muslim families live inside complex which take care of the tombs"</string>
    <string name="attraction_address_3">Gandhi Rd, Manek Chowk, Khadia, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380001</string>

    <string name="attraction_4">Nagina Wadi</string>
    <string name="attraction_description_4">"Nagina Wadi is a garden themed entertainment ground in the center of the circular Kankaria Lake at the Ahmedabad metropolitan area in Gujarat, India. Built for sole entertainment of the Mughal royals, Nagina Wadi is accessed by a straight, concrete, tree-lined walkway traversing half of the lake. In early 2009, the Ahmedabad Municipal Corporation (AMC) and AIL Amrapali Industries Limited ( Amrapali Group ) built and completed a large lighted musical fountain, featuring brilliant multicolored laser lights displayed during the night."</string>
    <string name="attraction_address_4">In Center of Kankaria Lake, Kankaria, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380002</string>

    //Food strings
    <string name="food_0">"Gordhan Thaal"</string>
    <string name="food_cuisine_0">"Gujarati"</string>
    <string name="food_description_0">"11 AM to 3 PM, 7 PM to 10:30 PM"
                "\nVegetarian Only"
                "\n₹600 for two people (approx.)"</string>
    <string name="food_address_0">"Ground Floor, Sapath Complex, Opposite Rajpath Club, S G Highway, Satellite, Ahmedabad\n"
                "079 26871222\n"
                "079 26873555\n"
                "079 26871222"</string>

    <string name="food_1">"Java - Courtyard By Marriott"</string>
    <string name="food_cuisine_1">"Cafe"</string>
    <string name="food_description_1">"6:30AM to 11:45PM\n"
                "₹1,000 for two people (approx.)"</string>
    <string name="food_address_1">"Courtyard By Marriott, Ramdevnagar Cross Road, Satellite, Ahmedabad\n"
                "079 30920625"</string>

    <string name="food_2">"Spezia Bistro &amp; Grills House"</string>
    <string name="food_cuisine_2">"European, Mexican, Italian"</string>
    <string name="food_description_2">"11 AM to 11 PM\n"
                "₹1,300 for two people (approx.)"</string>
    <string name="food_address_2">"Ground Floor, Acropolis Mall, S.G Highway, Thaltej, Ahmedabad\n"
                "079 30920346\n"
                "Table booking recommended"</string>

    <string name="food_3">"Hoglatto"</string>
    <string name="food_cuisine_3">"Desserts, Beverages"</string>
    <string name="food_description_3">"11 AM to 10:30 PM\n"
                "₹250 for two people (approx.)"</string>
    <string name="food_address_3">"GF/8, Galaxy Bazaar Complex, Opposite Himalaya Mall, Sunrise Park Road, Vastrapur, Ahmedabad"</string>

    //Hotel Strings
    <string name="hotel_0">"Ginger Hotel"</string>
    <string name="hotel_description_0">"Ginger Ahmedabad rooms have been thoughtfully designed keeping in mind the needs of a business &amp; leisure traveller. All rooms are equipped with comfortable bed and world class amenities which makes Ginger Hotel Ahmedabad one of the finest budget hotels in Ahmedabad."</string>
    <string name="hotel_address_0">"Ginger Hotel Ahmedabad, Behind Himalaya Mall, Drive-In road, Ahmedabad - 380 015"</string>

    <string name="hotel_1">"Hyatt Regency"</string>
    <string name="hotel_description_1">"Hyatt Regency Ahmedabad features 210 generously sized luxury rooms including 18 suites and one Presidential Suite. Guestrooms range from 33 to 150 square meters, with rich woods and textures, innovative materials and warm colours are the hallmarks of their design. These guestrooms offer the latest services and facilities to meet the needs of today’s travellers. "</string>
    <string name="hotel_address_1">"Hyatt Regency Ahmedabad\n"
                "17/A, Ashram Road\n"
                "Ahmedabad,  India, 380014\n"
                "Tel: 91 79 4017 1234"</string>

    <string name="hotel_2">"The Fern"</string>
    <string name="hotel_description_2">"A business hotel in Ahmedabad , The Fern, is Gujarat’s first ecotel. A contemporary hotel of 96 rooms and suites, the hotel is an elegant combination of European linear design and the deep roots of the traditional Gujarati themes. The hotel’s award-winning experience includes an exclusive club service, executive lounge, spa and indoor swimming pool."</string>
    <string name="hotel_address_2">"Nr. Sola Overbridge, S.G. Highway,, Ahmedabad Gujrat India -380054\n"
                "\n"
                "The Fern An Ecotel Hotel, Ahmedabad"</string>

    <string name="hotel_3">"Fortune Landmark"</string>
    <string name="hotel_description_3">"Conveniently located in the heart of the city, Fortune Landmark is an upscale, contemporary business hotel in Ahmedabad. The hotel offers first class services and facilities, combining comfort of home with Fortune Hotels’ efficient service."</string>
    <string name="hotel_address_3">"Fortune Landmark, Ahmedabad\n"
                "Ashram Road, Ahmedabad - 380013, Gujarat"</string>

    <string name="hotel_4">"Ramada"</string>
    <string name="hotel_description_4">"Our hotel features 2 meeting rooms, which can be arranged to accommodate 110 conference guests or 400 banquet guests. Plan your next meeting or special event with us. We also arrange great rates for groups — large or small."</string>
    <string name="hotel_address_4">"Ramada Ahmedabad\n"
                "Corporate Road, , Ahmedabad, 380015 IN\n"
                "9-191-794-0250000"</string>

    //Malls Strings
    <string name="mall_0">Alpha One</string>
    <string name="mall_description_0">AlphaOne Mall is a shopping mall located at Vastrapur, Ahmedabad, India. The mall was opened in October 2011 and is the largest mixed used city centre in Ahmedabad.</string>
    <string name="mall_address_0">Plot No-216, Vastrapur, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380006, India</string>

    <string name="mall_1">Himalaya Mall</string>
    <string name="mall_description_1">For casual shopping and Movie theater.</string>
    <string name="mall_address_1">Drive In Road, Nilmani Society, Memnagar, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380015</string>

    <string name="mall_2">Iscon Mega Mall</string>
    <string name="mall_description_2">Near Rajpath Club, SG Highway, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380054</string>
    <string name="mall_address_2">Near Rajpath Club, SG Highway, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380054</string>
</resources>
